Look,
it's downloading already.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. So, now you can ask if you have
any doubts.
>> Yeah.
Actually, I do have a question. Why we
are integrating like Claude with
Ollama, actually? We have multiple
options, right? Or else, we can use the
premium version of Claude.
>> Um
if we use premium version of Claude, we
have to pay. But, by integrating Ollama,
we are getting all the models
which are freely available and open
source. And are actually equivalent to
um Claude premium models
for free.
So, Ollama gives you free access to all
the models.
And
it has some restrictions for
um free usage.
But, that restriction is enough for a
beginner or for a
mediocre to slightly lower complex
projects.
And you will not get exhausted for those
limits.
>> Okay. Okay. That's good actually then.
It's kind of much more riskier for a
older version of systems to run this
command.
Especially if they're going with the
Ollama, right? It's better to like write
this command and go with
>> Not older version, but still uh since
it's a
complex process.
>> Heavy through. Yeah, it's a heavy and
you need
you require heavy processing for that,
right?
>> Yeah, heavy processing will be required.
And
for everyday modern LLMs, you can't run
it in older system as well.
>> Okay.
>> Okay, now we will start the
Ollama integration process.
>> Okay.
It seems fun.
>> Mhm.
So, give me energy vibes, bro.
>> Yeah.
Let's see.
>> Look, the magic will begin now.
It uh
It's taking a lot of time.
>> [clears throat]
>> Let's see.
Let's see again.
>> Okay, let's cut out the terminal and
reopen the terminal once again to see
how it processes.
>> Okay.
>> This way I will also show you how to
initiate
uh WSL from the start itself.
>> Sure.
>> So, for initiating WSL Linux, you have
to give this command.
WSL minus D
Ubuntu
Okay. So, it has been started.
>> No.
>> Okay. As I have told you,
we have to put this command once again.
>> So, it's installing, right?
>> Yeah, it's processing in the background.
>> Okay, it's processing.
Uh what's the size actually then?
>> [clears throat]
>> Size will be heavy.
You can say it's going to take up
>> around 6 GB 5 GB, right?
>> No, 15
GB.
>> Uh okay.
So
Can we change the drive also?
>> Yeah, you can change it by using CD
command.
>> Okay, the installation what about the
installation? Yeah, that will be on
that.
>> Installation will be on the default
drive itself, which is C drive, but you
can't change that path.
>> Okay.
>> You have enough space now?
>> Yeah, I do have, but in future if I want
to change the drive, so is it possible,
right?
There will be in lot not much more
hazards to perform.
>> You have to perform the installation
once again and
uh you have to do another steps
maybe to change those drives.
>> Okay.
>> Our installation is completed. Let me
just see how much storage
is left.
Again, 1
2 3 4 5 6 7
Yeah, it's good to go.
Okay, it's complete.
So, now we will run the command, but
before that,
you have to log in into your Ollama
account.
Okay.
>> Is this blog?
>> I don't know why this happened actually.
>> Yeah, let's see.
Okay, you do have GitHub account as
well, right?
>> Yeah, we can connect from there also.
>> Okay.
Maybe you have to sign up.
>> Mhm.
>> Wait, let's see.
Instead of signing up like directly, if
I do it this.
It will begin use sign up
from here I guess.
>> Okay.
>> Mhm.
Okay.
>> Okay, I'll call it a day when we meet.
Yeah, it's good to go.
>> Okay, wait. Let me reconnect. The screen
is hanging.
>> Yeah, I'm sure.
>> Okay.
Yeah.
Yep.
Uh you have logged into your account,
right?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. Now, I'll show you the interface
where you can check directly what is
your usage and all.
I go to the dashboard.
And here I'm signed in for
Okay, give your email address and then
>> We can directly log in, right?
>> No, do it inside from here.
From here
you are getting this small icon. Go to
settings.
We are in the settings. Now, go to
billing.
Here you can upgrade and here is the
main part of usage.
Here you will see all the usage that you
have been used. This usually resets in 1
hour
or sometimes takes 3 to 4 hours.
And you have get another usage which is
weekly usage.
>> Okay.
>> weekly usage, then it will reset after
the that
week's date is over.
>> Okay, after 1 week it will going to like
>> Reset, yeah.
>> Reset.
>> Okay, now we have to create keys as
well.
Add API key.
It's optional. Let's generate. Yep, it's
done. Now, go to the command prompt and
do Ollama sign in.
Ollama not found. Okay.
Okay, you have to also install Ollama as
well.
>> Okay.
>> In the terminal.
So
Use this command.
And it will directly download Ollama.
Give your password. For that sudo.
Okay, you have to also install this as
well.
As you can see how complex this process
is.
>> Okay.
It's about
the compatibility the version we are
installing. It should be like compatible
in this PC kind of.
>> Yeah.
Okay, it's installed. And now Ollama
will be also be installing.
It's completed. So, let's
again check
if it already has been set in the path
or not. Ollama.
>> Okay, good to go now, right?
>> Yeah.
We have to go to this link and it will
directly go to your dashboard.
And you have to
just click this button.
>> Okay.
>> This is all you have to do.
>> Now, don't we have to use the API key?
>> No, it will automatically integrate
to itself.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Now, for running it,
directly
either you can run like this or if this
command fails, you can run
with this command.
Cloud is not installed, okay.
>> Oh, Cloud is al- already installed,
right? In my PC that I'm currently
using, but in that particular location,
do we need to download Cloud also?
>> Uh maybe we have to also install Cloud
as well right now.
>> And Cloud will be like a particular
LLM.
>> No, it will be
>> or a particular
>> platform, Cloud Code and all. It will
give a direct access to our WSL.
>> Okay.
>> This is the NPM package we are
installing. By the help of
this NPM package, we will next install
the Cloud.
>> Okay.
Uh why this is mentioned this way?
Use code with caution caution.
>> That's a generally every LLM
uh uses that warning sign.
Cuz they are uncertain and we are
getting this result from
Google cell LM actually.
>> Okay.
>> This is my box.
Okay, finally it's completed.
Now, let's start this install.
I don't have permission right.
I don't have access.
Let's start the next directory.
We have to give permission access to
this.
Let's see what we can do here.
>> Do we need to go to cloud and do the
like developer kind of stuff access?
>> It will directly download it.
Wait for a minute.
And we ran this command actually.
It started itself.
Then why did it not run?
Quick fix using soda.
Okay, soda will run.
Added three packages. Now, let's see.
Okay, it's started.
And we have some
And we also get
other models as well.
Like, if you want to
do something
we have this Gemma 431B.
And if you want to like download in your
local system rather than learning
running it from the cloud you could also
download these models.
And
>> Okay.
>> Uh,
there are other models as well.
Like, go to dashboard.
Hm, models.
And here you will get a list of all the
models it has as of now.
>> Okay, and every model has its own
benefit and limitations, right?
>> Limitation and use cases. Coding models
are separate, vision models are
separate, reasoning models are separate.
So, you have to choose it as per your
problem use case.
>> Anything I can use here?
>> Uh local you are asking?
>> Uh not local uh yes, locally.
>> Locally, you have to choose some
lightweight model
like uh
uh
if you want
you can choose
>> Okay, any lightweight model we can use
locally?
Mhm.
>> Yeah.
>> And from the cloud if we are using
>> Mhm.
And look, this is a lightweight model, I
guess.
13.6
versus 27 billion, 35 No, it's also a I
heavy weight model as well.
Let's search when
because when models are very powerful
and you can
trust on them.
>> Okay.
>> 2.5
2.5 coder. This is a lightweight model
and it's a coding model as well.
>> Okay.
>> For this, you can use this.
And
either directly put like this
or you can
give another command ollama pull when
2.5.
And now it's downloading.
After downloading
>> Mhm.
>> you will get a
same interface where we got earlier
selection process, right? There you will
get this particular model listed and you
can select it from there.
>> Okay. So,
it will add from in that list, right?
>> Yeah, it will add in that list.
>> But that list
where like
using from the
internet, right? They're directly
connected with the internet.
>> No, this one you are running it from
local model, so it will run from your
local PC's processing and all.
Since it's a local model, not a cloud.
>> Not a cloud.
>> Yeah, and cloud models are basically 10
to 15 MB.
>> Okay.
>> Okay, so this was the whole process and
your problem of Ollama is completely
solved.
Here it's replying.
Okay.
>> Yeah, that was
Yeah, actually this was fun installing
it. A lot of hassles and a lot of like
a lot to do in order to install locally,
right?
>> Yeah.
Okay, so we can end the session right
now.
>> Yeah, thank you for this insightful
session. I will
>> Okay, thanks. Bye-bye. Fine and
>> Bye.